http://www.willespie.com.au/privacy_policy_and_terms_conditions.html

Contact
Terms and ConditionsThe www.willespie.com.au website (Web Site) is created and controlled by Hopestar P/L ABN 46078087671 (we, our or us). Age RequirementYou may only enter and use this Web Site if you are aged 18 years or over or otherwise over the legal drinking age in your country of residence.  You must immediately exit the Web Site if you do not meet these requirements. The use of this Web Site is governed by the following terms and conditions of use, as amended from time to time (the "Terms and Conditions"). If you use this Web Site (and each time you use it) you acknowledge to us that you have read and understood these Terms and Conditions and agree to be bound by them. Online AccountIn order to purchase goods and services from us we may require that you open an account on the Web Site, in which case we will provide you with an account username and password. You must keep your account username and password details confidential and secure from unauthorised use, you must not allow any other person to use your account or allow any person under the age of 18 to use your account to order goods from us. You agree that you are solely responsible for all activity that occurs on your account, including the purchase of any goods.  You also agree that you will be responsible for the conduct of any person who uses your account, whether or not you have authorised that use. If you become aware of any breach of security or unauthorised access to or use of your account, you must immediately notify us by contacting info@willespie.com.au. DisclaimerThis website is for information purposes only. We make every effort to ensure that the contents of this website are true and accurate. However, we make no warranty as to the completeness, accuracy or reliability of such contents and we exclude, to the maximum extent permissible by law, any and all implied terms and warranties. It is your responsibility to acquire and maintain appropriate and up to date virus scanning software and to carry out a virus check on any file, download or attachment for viruses prior to downloading. We do not warrant that any file, download, link, feed or attachment on this website is free from viruses or other errors or defects and by using this website you are taken to accept these risks. To the maximum extent permitted by law, we and our directors, employees, agents or contractors and related companies exclude all liability (except where precluded by law) for any loss or damage caused (whether in tort or otherwise and whether directly or indirectly) by accessing this website, an inability to access this website, any virus transmitted through this website or your use of, or reliance on, any information or data obtained from this website. If you are dissatisfied with this website, your sole remedy is to discontinue use of it. Links to Third Party Sites and Third Party AdvertisementsThere may be links to other web sites or advertisements of goods and services available from other parties on our Web Site.  We are not responsible for those web sites, their content or the goods and services available on them.  Privacy Policyeffective 25th May 2018  This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information from individuals who sign up to receive our newsletters and information of forthcoming events. The GDPR that has recently come into effect is designed to protect you from privacy and data breaches. Your consent to the collection and storage of your personal information must be freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous. 1. Email and personal details. Willespie Wines sell wine, food and gifts at the Winery’s Cellar Door, wine purchases on our website and host regular events and weddings at the Winery in Willyabrup. 1a) In exchange for information about our products and events your name, email address, telephone number and other contact details are frequently requested. These details are stored securely as a means to identify individuals either directly or indirectly. 1b) Any personal information is kept secure and can only be accessed by authorised personnel who work directly with Willespie Wines.Willespie uses Mailchimp to maintain their marketing lists. Mailchimp adheres strictly to the privacy laws here. 1c) For wine purchases using PayPal via our website, your credit card details are never retained. The privacy policy for PayPal can be viewed here.  2. Cookies Cookies are temporary, small pieces of information sent to a visitor’s hard disk. They do not track your behaviour, spread viruses or run programs. Most website browsers are set up to accept cookies. You may choose to reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally with instructions on how to do this being accessible under Help on your toolbar. 2a) Some of our web pages provide may contain links to third party websites. Please be aware that we have no access to or control over their practices and as a result are not responsible for their content or privacy notices. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personal information. 2b) If you wish to enquire about the personal data held by Willespie Wines please email admin@willespie.com.au 3. Retention and Deletion 3a) At the bottom of every email sent by Willespie Wines you will find an unsubscribe button that enables you to stop receiving all automated communications with immediate effect. 3b) If you would prefer your personal details to be de-identified following purchase of a product, this can be done and replaced with a generic non-identifiable number. 3c) Willespie Wines are committed to protecting the privacy of children and therefore they do not seek to collect any data from those known to be under the age of 18. 4. Acceptance of Conditions 4a) Willespie Wines have the right to assume that all visitors have read this notice carefully, especially when explicitly agreeing to terms and conditions that have been outlined. This Privacy Policy will be updated as required and with new versions being identifiable through the use of versioning details. 5. Sharing of Information 5a) Other than when running a co-hosted event, your data will never be shared, rented or sold to third parties 5b) The only time a person’s personal information would be divulged would be when required by law. 6. Further Information 6a) If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact admin@willespie.com.au6b) All information, products and services are provided for general information and education purposes. Nothing on this site should be interpreted as professional advice. 7. Business Details ABN 46 078 087 671 Country: Australia Unless otherwise stated all prices quoted are in Australian Dollars Email: admin@willespie.com.auWebsite: www.willespie.com.au 8. Contacting Us Willespie Wines welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any question or require further information please contact us by email admin@willespie.com.au
